<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_and_notification_dashboard_summary">Assistant, recent apps, default apps</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_activation_warning">When you\'re connected, you can still access photos and videos at the quality you selected for backup</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_days_title">Remove backed up photos &amp; videos</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_deactivation_warning">Turn off Smart Storage? \n\nSmart Storage won\'t free up space when your storage is almost full.</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_preference_title">Smart Storage</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_primary_switch_title">Use Smart Storage</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_settings">Smart Storage</string>
    <string name="automatic_storage_manager_text">When storage is almost full, remove backed up photos and videos. You can still find them in Google Photos.</string>
    <string name="battery_tip_limited_temporarily_extra_summary">To protect your battery, charging is paused at %1$s while your tablet is docked</string>
    <string name="content_capture">Personalize using app data</string>
    <string name="dark_ui_text">Dark theme uses a black background to help keep your battery alive longer. Dark theme schedules wait to turn on until your screen is off.</string>
    <string name="display_white_balance_summary">Dynamically adjusts the display based on surrounding light levels</string>
    <string name="display_white_balance_title">Ambient EQ</string>
    <string name="double_twist_for_camera_mode_summary">To switch in and out of selfie mode in Google Camera, double-twist when you’re in the app.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_unlock_set_unlock_password">Pixel Imprint + Password</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_unlock_set_unlock_pattern">Pixel Imprint + Pattern</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_unlock_set_unlock_pin">Pixel Imprint + PIN</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_unlock_skip_fingerprint">Continue without Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_unlock_title">With Pixel Imprint, you can unlock your phone using your fingerprint. For security, this option requires a backup screen lock.</string>
    <string name="gesture_double_twist_sensor_type">com.google.sensor.double_twist</string>
    <string name="gesture_double_twist_sensor_vendor">Google</string>
    <string name="lock_settings_picker_fingerprint_message">Choose a backup screen lock to use with Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="owner_info_settings_edit_text_hint">E.g., Joe’s Pixel.</string>
    <string name="rtt_settings_always_visible">Always visible</string>
    <string name="rtt_settings_no_visible">Not visible</string>
    <string name="rtt_settings_title">Real-time text (RTT)</string>
    <string name="rtt_settings_visible_during_call">Visible during call</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_consent_introduction_title">Allow Face Unlock</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_education_message">On the next screen, rotate your head to capture all angles of your face</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_education_message_accessibility">On the next screen, hold your phone at eye level</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_finish_title">Looks good!</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility">Setup for limited vision or head motion</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility_expanded">When using Face Unlock, your head may need to be more directly in front of your phone.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_accessibility_vision">Require eyes open</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_consent_message">Using your child’s face to unlock their phone may be less secure than a strong pattern or PIN.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_consent_message">You and your child can delete their face model or turn off Face Unlock at any time in Settings. Face models are stored on the phone until they’re deleted.\n\nLearn more at g.co/pixel/faceunlock.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_consent_title">You and your child are in control</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_message">You can delete your face model or turn off Face Unlock at any time in Settings. Face models are stored on the phone until you delete them.\n\nLearn more at g.co/pixel/faceunlock.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_control_title">You’re in control</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_consent_message">Face Unlock creates a unique model of your child’s face to verify it’s them. To create this face model during setup, your child will take images of their face from different angles.\n\nWhen they use Face Unlock, images are used to update their face model. Images used to create their face model are not stored, but the face model is stored securely on the phone and never leaves the phone. All processing occurs securely on the phone.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_message">Face Unlock creates a unique model of your face to verify it’s you. To create this face model during setup, you will take images of your face from different angles.\n\nWhen you use Face Unlock, images are used to update your face model. Images used to create your face model are not stored, but the face model is stored securely on your phone and never leaves the phone. All processing occurs securely on your phone.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_how_title">How it works</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_gaze">Face Unlock can require your child’s eyes to be open to unlock the phone or verify it’s them. You and your child can turn this option on at any time in Settings.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_glasses">If your child normally wears eyeglasses, they can wear them during setup.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_less_secure">Using your child’s face to unlock their phone may be less secure than a strong pattern, PIN, or password</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_consent_looking">Looking at the phone can unlock it even when they don’t intend to. Their phone can also be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like them, like an identical sibling, or if someone holds it up to their face.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_gaze">Face Unlock can require your eyes to be open to unlock the phone or verify it’s you. You can turn this option on at any time in Settings.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_glasses">Glasses or lightly tinted sunglasses are OK.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_less_secure">Using your face to unlock your phone may be less secure than a strong pattern, PIN, or password</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_looking">Looking at the phone can unlock it even when you don’t intend to. Your phone can also be unlocked by someone who looks a lot like you, like an identical sibling, or if someone holds it up to your face.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_face_enroll_introduction_info_title">Keep in mind</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_consent_introduction_title">Allow Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_disclaimer">In addition to unlocking your phone, you can also use Pixel Imprint to authorize purchases and app access. Learn more</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_introduction_footer_message_1">The data recorded by Pixel Imprint is stored securely and never leaves your phone. You can delete your data anytime in Settings.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_introduction_message">Pixel Imprint uses your fingerprint to wake and unlock your phone, authorize purchases, or sign in to apps.\n\nBe careful whose fingerprints you add. Any fingerprints added will be able to do these things. Learn more</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_introduction_message_unlock_disabled">With Pixel Imprint, you can use your fingerprint to authorize purchases or sign in to apps.\n\nBe careful whose fingerprints you add. Any fingerprints added will be able to do these things.\n\nNote: You can’t use your fingerprint to unlock this device. For more information, contact your organization’s admin.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_introduction_title">Set up Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_enroll_introduction_title_unlock_disabled">Unlock with Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_preference_summary_none">Tap to set up fingerprint</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_preference_title">Pixel Imprint</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_v2_enroll_introduction_footer_message_2">Pixel Imprint creates a unique model of your fingerprint to verify it’s you. To create this fingerprint model during setup, you will take images of your fingerprint from different positions.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_v2_enroll_introduction_footer_message_4">You can delete your fingerprint model, or turn off Pixel Imprint at any time in Settings. Fingerprint models are stored on the phone until you delete them.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_v2_enroll_introduction_footer_message_consent_2">Pixel Imprint creates a unique model of your child’s fingerprint to verify it’s them. To create this fingerprint model during setup, they will take images of their fingerprint from different positions.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_v2_enroll_introduction_footer_message_consent_4">You and your child can delete their fingerprint model, or turn off Pixel Imprint at any time in Settings. Fingerprint models are stored on the phone until they’re deleted.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_fingerprint_v2_enroll_introduction_message_learn_more">Learn more about Pixel fingerprint unlock at &lt;a href=\'http://g.co/pixel/fingerprintunlock\'&gt;g.co/pixel/fingerprintunlock&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
    <string name="security_settings_work_fingerprint_preference_title">Pixel Imprint for work</string>
    <string name="setup_fingerprint_enroll_finish_message">Just touch the Pixel Imprint sensor to wake and unlock your phone.</string>
    <string name="suggested_fingerprint_lock_settings_summary">Use Pixel Imprint to unlock your phone</string>
</resources>
